m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0
m 115 64 l 115 35 l 171 0 l 177 0 l 133 46 l 143 52 l 179 0 l 184 0 l 159 63 l 229 107 l 229 182 l 145 96 l 135 122 l 207 227 l 137 227 l 115 172 l 115 93 l 126 76 l 115 64 l 104 76 l 115 93 l 115 172 l 93 227 l 23 227 l 95 122 l 84 96 l 0 182 l 0 107 l 70 63 l 45 0 l 50 0 l 87 52 l 97 46 l 52 0 l 59 0 l 115 35
m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60
m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172
人人影视
YYeTs.com
原创翻译  双语字幕
■
仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新
请登陆www.YYeTs.com
翻译：红果  阿蘅阿蘅  猫中之王  12CC醉芝士
校对： 90分钟赛太公  天天夜夜YY猫总监   YY
后期：孤帆    时间轴：加森
老爸老妈浪漫史
第八季  第二十集
孩子们  2013年4月
Kids, in April of 2013,
2030年
我和你们的妈妈住得很近
your mother and I were very close
却互不相识
and yet very far apart.
我住在西82街
I was living on West 82nd Street.
她住西115街
She was up on West 115th.
她在攻读经济学学位
She was getting a degree in economics.
我在大学里教建筑学
I was teaching architecture.
我总是光顾麦凯伦酒吧
I was always at MacLaren's.
她总是
She was always...
不怎么去酒吧
not spending all her time in a bar.
当时她跟一个叫路易斯的金融男约会
She was dating some finance guy named Louis.
纳苏街  华尔街
而我呢
And I...
孤身一人
I was alone.
泰德  马上你会被一群
Ted, get ready to be surrounded by
全身抹油的半裸体包围着
half-naked, grease-covered bodies.
我说的油  是指汽车润滑油
And by grease, I mean motor grease.
我们要去看机器人大战摔跤手啦
We're going to Robots vs. Wrestlers!
孩子们  你们还记得机器人大战摔跤手吧
Kids, you remember Robots vs. Wrestlers.
忘掉一切有关
Forget everything you remember
机器人大战摔跤手的记忆
about Robots vs. Wrestlers.
这次是机器人大战摔跤手之传奇大战
This is Robots vs. Wrestlers: "Legends."
高龄摔跤手对抗老爷机器人
Elderly wrestlers fighting old-timey robots
场地是一个轮椅摔跤台
in a wheelchair-accessible wrestling ring.
我们为什么还坐在这儿
Why are we still sitting here?
我明天有堂重要的课
I got a big lecture tomorrow.
今晚就不折腾了
Think I'm gonna take it easy tonight.
泰德  相信我  20年以后
Ted, trust me, 20 years from now,
你会庆幸自己见证了这场传奇大战
you'll be glad you saw Robots vs. Wrestlers: Legends.
我想象不出来这种可能性
I can't imagine a world where that's possible.
我是认真的
I'm serious.
二十年后
20 years from now,
我第三任26岁的妻子问我这场比赛
when my 26-year-old third wife asks me about this...
这种玩笑你开得太多了
You make a lot of those jokes.
我会说
I'm gonna say,
"太精彩了  但你知道最搞笑的是什么吗
"Yeah, it was awesome, but you know the funny thing?
泰德差点就没去"
Ted almost didn't go."
"但是感谢上帝他去了  那晚太精彩了"
"But thank God he did, because it was a great night."
然后我们会转战到按摩浴缸
And then she and I will adjourn to the Jacuzzi,
我的第四任妻子在那里等我们
where my fourth wife will be waiting for us,
她已经在喷水口那里自嗨了
already warming herself up on the jets.
罗宾来了  剩下的等会再说
Oh, Robin's here-- I'll tell you the rest later.
记得要说  这故事有无限可能
Please do, that story could go anywhere.
我们又到酒吧来了
Here we are at the bar once more.
你们会问"我们该喝什么呢"
"What will I have to drink?" You ask.
明尼苏达海啸
Minnesota Tidal Wave.
你们会问"那是什么玩意"
"What's that?" You ask.
史上最好喝的鸡尾酒
Only the best cocktail ever.
你们再问"是谁发明的"
"Who invented it?" You ask.
我
Me.
这可不是女性饮品
And it's not a girly drink.
莉莉  你干嘛说那几个字
Lily, why would you even say that?
女性饮品
Girly drink.
我世界上最不女人的女人
Hey, I am the least girly girl on Earth,
我就很喜欢明尼苏达海啸
and I love the Minnesota Tidal Wave.
谢谢  罗宾
Thank you, Robin.
实际上  我要去点一杯
Matter of fact, I'm going to go order one
并且要昂首挺胸地走过去
right now with my head held high.
-莉莉  -你想让我帮你点吗
- Lily. - You want me to order it for you?
是的  谢谢宝贝
Yes, please, thank you, baby.
泰德  我告诉你生活的秘诀是什么
Ted, let me tell you the secret to life.
每次我要决定
Every time I make a decision
要在某个夜晚干点什么时  我就问自己
about what to do on a given night, I ask myself,
"干什么会变成二十年后最美好的记忆"
"What would make the best memory 20 years from now?"
所以我让二十年后的巴尼替我决定
So I let 20-Years-From-Now- Barney call the shots.
每次都能奏效
And it always works out.
二十年后的巴尼
And 20-Years-From-Now-Barney
认为我们应该去看机器人大战摔跤手
thinks we should go to Robots vs. Wrestlers?
我不知道  问问他吧
I don't know. Let's ask him.
闭上眼睛  泰德
Close your eyes, Ted.
好  现在睁开
Okay, now open them.
巴尼  我发誓
Barney, I swear to God,
如果我睁开眼睛看见你的光腚
if I open my eyes and your bare ass
又紧贴着我的脸
is an inch away from my face again...
快睁开眼
Just open your eyes.
泰德  这是二十年后的巴尼
Ted, I'd like you to meet 20-Years-From-Now-Barney.
二十年后的巴尼  你记得泰德吧
20-Years-From-Now-Barney, you remember Ted.
你好啊
'Sup?
泰德
Hey, Ted.
我听说并记得
What's this I hear-slash-remember
你不想去看机器人大战摔跤手  是吗
about you not wanting to see Robots vs. Wrestlers?
是的  我就是不想去而已
Yeah, it's just that I don't want to see it.
-你不...  -我知道
- You don't... - I know.
-他不...  -我知道
- He doesn't... - I know.
泰德  相信我们  这将是一场传...
Ted, trust us, it's gonna be legend--
再等个20年
wait 20 years for it...
奇
...dary!
-传奇  -传奇
- Legendary! - Legendary!
好了  我要回家了
Okay, uh, I'm gonna go home.
-听着  泰德  -别走
- No, Ted, look. - Come on!
如果你不相信机器人大战摔跤手
If you don't believe that robots vs. Wrestlers
将会是你人生的转折点
is gonna be a life-changing event,
或许你会相信二十年后的泰德
maybe you'll believe 20-Years-From-Now-Ted.
你好啊
'Sup?
突然要消化这么多东西
Wow, so many things all at once.
但是最重要的是
But most importantly...
我居然没有秃顶
I don't go bald?
没
Nope.
我也没秃
And neither do I.
泰德  听我说
Ted, listen to me.
你  听你说
You, listen to you.
也就是我
Me.
你必须去看机器人大战摔跤手之传奇大战
You got to go to Robots vs. Wrestlers: Legends.
相信我  不去看的话你会后悔的
Trust me, you will regret it if you don't.
到底是什么  我会秃顶还是怎样
So, what, do I go bald or something?
那是假发吗
Is that a toupee?
-泰德  检查头皮  -不能叫罗宾吗
- Ted, scalp check! - Can't Robin do this?
快点  你都给我检查好几年了
Come on, you've been doing it for years.
你知道参比依据
You know the frame of reference.
头皮检查
Scalp check!
真稀奇
Hmm, that's odd.
这周检查头皮的时间略早啊
Little early in the week for scalp check.
5大汤匙糖
Five tablespoons of sugar,
再一点点香草伏特加
a whisper of vanilla vodka
就大功告成了
and you're done.
酒浸樱桃
Maraschino cherries.
最后在上面加点酒浸樱桃
Oh, and a handful of maraschino cherries on top.
等一下  你们点的是罗宾・特布罗斯基
Wait, you're ordering a Robin Scherbatsky.
干嘛不直接说
Why didn't you just say that?
等等  酒吧老板
One second there, barkeep.
我要是没记错的话
Unless I'm mistaken,
这位女士刚刚点的是
the drink this lady just ordered
明尼苏达海啸
is called the Minnesota Tidal Wave.
发明人未知
Origin unknown.
罗宾最近总是点这种酒
Oh, well, you know, Robin's been ordering them so much lately
所以我们以她的名字命名了
that we named it after her.
你们用我的名字做酒名
You named a drink after me?
菜单上写着呢
Right there in the menu.
恭喜
Congrats.
鸡尾酒
罗宾・特布罗斯基
肖恩・惠勒
蔻可拉舒尔
我喝不下去了
I can't drink this.
这样好点  我还是很火大
That's better. I'm still seething,
不过这样好点
but that's better.
好吧  二十年后的我
Okay, 20-Years-From-Now-Me,
和我说实话
level with me.
你们  我们
You. Us.
"机器人大战摔跤手"值得看吗
Is Robots vs. Wrestlers worth it?
那是我此生最棒的一晚
It was the single greatest night of my life.
甚至比你婚礼那天还棒吗
Even greater than your wedding?
不  等真到了我结婚那天
Well, I mean, when I get married,
那肯定是我此生最棒的一晚
that'll be the greatest night of my life.
不过谁知道我会不会结婚呢
But who knows when that's going to happen?
天啊  你还没...
Oh, my God, you still haven't...
我希望早日与她邂逅
Man, I hope I meet her soon.
天啊  我到底怎么了
Oh, God, what is wrong with me?!
抱歉
I'm sorry!
我逗你玩呢
I'm just messing with you!
快决定  是去还是不去
Now, come on, are we going or what?
行  走吧
Fine, let's go.
别着急啊
Not so fast.
巴尼  泰德  二十年后的巴尼
Barney, Ted, 20-Years-From-Now-Barney,
二十年后的泰德
20-Years-From-Now-Ted.
你是谁
Who are you?
我是二十小时后的泰德
I'm 20-Hours-From-Now-Ted.
你们这群混蛋哪也不准去
And you bastards aren't going anywhere.
你是二十小时后的泰德
So, you're the Ted from 20 hours from now?
你没事吧
You okay?
我有事
No, I'm not okay.
这蠢货要去看"机器人大战摔跤手"
This dummy's about to go to Robots vs. Wrestlers--
没错  那绝对会精彩绝伦
and yes, it'll be awesome...
看到没
See?
一开始精彩
...at first.
但很快你就会饮酒过多
But then you're gonna drink way too much,
然后就会头疼
hence the headache.
再然后你就会跳上拳击场
Then you're gonna jump into the ring
扭伤你的手腕  所以手腕有夹板
and sprain your wrist, hence the splint.
再之后
And then afterwards,
你就会抽半包香烟  于是...
you're gonna smoke half a pack of cigarettes, hence the...
听起来挺不错的嘛
Well, that's the sound a good time.
二十小时后  当你变成我的时候
And 20 hours from now, when you're me,
你会想回到这里
you're gonna want to come back here,
回到这个卡座前  回到这一分钟
right to this very spot, right now,
狠狠地扇自己一耳光
and smack yourself upside the head.
但显然我不会那么做
Yeah, but obviously I wouldn't do that
因为想让扇自己除非...
'cause I'd only be smacking myself--
别这么对我  泰德  别这样对我们
Don't do this to me, Ted. Don't do this to us.
别听你的  现在的泰德
Don't listen to yourself, Present-Day-Ted.
这是一辈子都值得回味的一天
It's a day of pain for a lifetime of memories.
二十小时后的我
20-Hours-From-Now-Me,
告诉我一件事  我吐了吗
just tell me one thing: do I hurl?
吐了  孩子
Yeah, kid.
你吐了
You hurl.
吐得很厉害吗
A lot?
还记得妈妈
Remember when Mom
从特价店买回来的变质牛肉吗
bought the beef from the Price Club?
好吧  这样行不行
Okay, how about this:
我们去看机器人大战摔跤手
we go to Robots vs. Wrestlers,
但我不会过多饮酒
but I don't drink too much?
有意思
Interesting.
我同意
I'm good with that.
不  算了吧
No, forget it.
如果泰德不喝醉
If Ted doesn't get wasted,
他最后根本不可能
there's no way he'll end up making out
和超真实的女机器人亲热
with that surprisingly realistic-looking female robot.
等等  我亲了女机器人吗
Wait, I kiss a female robot?
你可不止亲亲哦
Oh, you do a lot more than that.
没人说非得喝酒
Now, look, nobody is saying you need alcohol
才能度过一个激动难忘的夜晚
to have an exciting and memorable night.
-那是  -当然
- Absolutely not. - Absolutely not.
不过这件事情  你是必须先喝醉
But in this case, yeah, you kind of have to be wasted.
你还得喝一大桶啤酒
You drink beers in cans still.
这会机器人看起来更恐怖
It makes the robot scarier.
他们居然以她命名我的酒
They named my drink after her.
明尼苏达海啸
The Minnesota Tidal Wave.
那是我常喝的酒
It's my usual.
这无关紧要
Immaterial!
如果这酒要以一个人的名字命名
If it's gonna be named after anybody,
那应该叫"马修・埃里克森"
it should be called The Marshall Eriksen.
抱歉  事实是"罗宾・特布罗斯基"
Sorry, it's The Robin Scherbatsky.
接受事实  一边哭去吧
Read it and weep.
那你是要偷我的创意吗
Oh, so you're gonna Zuckerberg me?
是吗
That it?
偷窃我的创意
You're Zuckerberging me?
好吧
That's fine.
法庭上见
I'll see you in court.
称之为"舞池"的小法庭
Little court known as the dance floor.
舞蹈对决  现在
Dance-off. Now.
不  不要跳舞
No, no dancing.
马修  我们已经说好了
Marshall, we've been through this.
医生说你屁股的状况相当糟糕
The doctor said your dancer's hip is worse than ever.
你得休息一阵子别扭了
You have to lay off dancing for a while.
你这不是要我的命吗  莉莉
You're killing me, Lily!
你是要我的命啊
You're killing me!
我是个成年人
I'm an adult.
我要以舞赢得我的尊严之战
You have to let me dance my own battles.
马修  不用什么舞蹈对决
Marshall, there's not gonna be a dance-off
因为酒名已经定了
because the name is staying.
就这样  问题解决
Period, end of story.
我就喜欢我的名字被写在上面
I just like having my name on something.
是吗
Oh, you do?
很好  罗宾
Oh, that's great, Robin.
你会心想事成
Then that's what you will get.
你会
That's...
心想
what you...
事成
will get.
两分钟后
罗宾
Oh, hey, Robin.
知道什么是《激情热线》吗
You here "For a good time"?
《For a Good Time, Call... 》喜剧电影
经典之作
Classic.
你是把我的电话号码写在男厕里吗
Did you write my number in the men's room?
那个  我不知道
It... Well, I don't know.
除非你进去  不然你绝不会知道
I guess you'll never know unless you go in there,
我肯定你不敢...
which I highly doubt that...
她进去了
There she goes.
小伙子们
Okay, boys.
闭上眼睛  关上鸟笼
Close your eyes and zip your flies.
当我不存在
Hi. Don't mind me.
想激情一下吗
请致电罗宾・特布罗斯基
你不应该那么做的
I don't think you should have done that.
莉莉  我知道我在做什么
Lily, I know what I'm doing, all right?
我是一名律师
I'm a lawyer.
我已经预想过各种状况了
I've thought about every possible scenario.
我已经遥遥领先于...
I'm ten steps ahead of...
她要去哪里
Where's she going?
大概是去女厕
Probably into the ladies' room
在墙上乱写点你的什么吧
to write something on the wall about you.
女厕的墙上
Nobody writes things
才没有人乱涂乱画呢
on the walls of the ladies' room.
你去过女厕吗
Have you been in the ladies' room?
当然没去过
Of course not.
莉莉  在下虽然具备坏男孩的各种性感魅力
Lily, I know that I have the sexual charisma of a bad boy,
但我绝对没有他们的不良习气
but I certainly don't have the manners of one.
你在里面写了什么
What'd you write in there?
你何不自己进去看一看呢
Why don't you go in and look?
你明知道我做不出这种事  罗宾
You know I can't do that, Robin.
莉莉  帮我进去看一看吧
Lily, can you go look?
我记得你不是想要独舞迎战吗
Oh, I thought you wanted to dance your own battles.
各位女士  把裙子都穿上了
Ladies, put your blouses back on!
在下要进来了
I'm coming in!
亲爱的马修
Dear Marshall,
我知道这种道歉方式实在很奇怪
I know this is a strange way to apologize,
但抱歉卡尔用我名字命名你的酒
but I'm sorry I let Carl name your drink after me.
我为什么当时不反对呢
Why didn't I say something?
这大概得追溯到我的悲惨童年
Gosh, I guess that goes back to my childhood.
好了各位
Okay, guys.
我们去看机器人大战摔跤手吧
Let's go to Robots vs. Wrestlers.
太好了  你总算想明白了
Huzzah! Now you're talking!
-走吧  -不  都给我坐好
- Here we go. - Nope, sit down.
统统给我坐好
Everybody sit down.
你是哪位啊
Okay, who are you?
泰德  巴尼  二十小时后的泰德
Hello, Ted, Barney, 20-Hours-From-Now-Ted,
二十年后的泰德  二十年后的巴尼  你们好
20-Years-From-Now-Ted, 20-Years-From-Now-Barney.
最近过得怎么样
Hey, how's it going?
容我自我介绍一下
Allow me to introduce myself.
我是二十分钟后的巴尼
I'm 20-Minutes-From-Now-Barney,
我有非常重要的事要...
and I have got something very important to...
你衣服上的污渍是怎么回事  老兄
What's the stain on your shirt, bro?
拜托  拜托
Please, please,
我真的有非常重要的事
I really do have something very important to...
你看起来好蠢
You look stupid.
你的意大利面来了
Here's your spaghetti.
小心
And be careful...
那些肉丸子
...with the meatball.
那是我爸爸唯一一次
And that's the only time my father
说他为我而骄傲
ever said he was proud of me.
也许这就是为什么我抢走了你的酒名
Maybe that's why I stole credit for your drink.
也许这就是
Maybe that's why
我要用这种方式倾吐心声的原因
I needed to pour my heart out like this.
又或许我是为了让你在女厕多待一会
Or, maybe I wrote this so you'd be in here long enough
直到有女士进来  让你吓得躲进隔间里
for a lady to walk in, causing you to freak out
才写了这么多东西
and hide in the stall.
你收到了短信
So, you got a text message?
我说中了吧
爱你的  罗宾
罗宾・特布罗斯基鸡尾酒发明者
下次记得把饭往嘴里送
Try to get some in your mouth next time.
好了各位  听我说
Okay, everybody, listen up.
我刚进来的时候
When I walked in here,
我还是二十分钟之后的巴尼
I was 20-Minutes- From-Now-Barney.
但那是十九分钟前
But that was 19 minutes
"我现在有点倒胃反酸
and some serious acid reflux--
谁会在爱尔兰酒吧点意大利粉吃"的事了
who orders spaghetti at an Irish bar?-- ago.
现在我是二十秒之后的巴尼
Now, i'm 20-Seconds- From-Now-Barney,
我告诉你们  注意看那扇门
and I'm telling you, watch that door.
为什么
Why?
这就是为什么
That's why.
再等个十二秒左右
In-in, like, 12 seconds.
你的皮肤看起来真紧致
Your skin looks great.
谢谢
Thanks.
多亏了你一直注意保养
And thank you for taking such good care of it.
这就是为什么
That's why.
那是谁
Who is that?
她是在我们七年前去过的舞厅
She's the coat check girl
看衣帽间的姑娘
from that dance club we went to seven years ago.
你记得那个晚上吧
You remember that night.
巴尼和他表妹磨蹭了一晚上
When Barney grinded with his cousin.
拜托  都二十年了你还记得啊
Oh, man, you remember that 20 years from now?
他还生怕别人会忘记
He won't let anyone forget.
衣帽间的姑娘
Coat check girl.
我一直想回去那家俱乐部
I always meant to go back to that club
要她的电话号码  可我没有回去
and get her number, but I didn't.
而现在她出现在这里
And now she's here?
七年之后出现在这间酒吧里
She's in this bar seven years later?
我简直不敢相信
I-I can't believe this.
你们觉得我应该过去和她说话吗
So, wait, do you guys think I should go talk to her?
-你开玩笑呢  -当然快去
- Are you kidding me? - Yes, go...
-你要我说多少遍  -大笨蛋
- How many different ways... - Idiot.
你好
Hello?
请问有人在外面吗
Is anybody out there?
听起来外面没有人了
Sounds like the coast is clear.
别走  别走  等等
No, no, wait!
拜托  真不是我的错
Please, it's not my fault!
我是被人陷害的
I was tricked!
这样可不好  马修
Not cool, Marshall.
这是一间高级酒吧
This is a nice bar.
姑娘们上这里来  只是为了和朋友放松
Girls come here, they just want to relax with their friends,
喝上几杯罗宾・特布罗斯基
maybe have a few Robin Scherbatskys,
而不是提心吊胆
and not have to worry out some guy
害怕有人在厕所搞什么马修・埃瑞克森之举
pulling a Marshall Eriksen in the bathroom.
不  我知道  我只是
No, no, no, I know. I just...
等一下  你刚才是不是用我的名字
Wait a minute, did you just use my name
来指代变态行为了
as shorthand for a guy being creepy?
没错
Yep.
你知道吗  卡尔
Well, you know what, Carl?
我觉得你的行为
I think that you are making
是不分是非黑白乱扣帽子
a broad and prejudicial assumption.
所以下次我看到有人冒出来
So next time I meet a guy who just goes around
妄加评论的时候  我会说
rushing to judgment, I'm gonna say,
"哇  那家伙真是好卡尔..."
"Hey, that guy's being a real Carl..."
你不知道我姓什么是吧
You don't know my last name.
你在这里都喝了这么多年了
You've been drinking here for years,
居然还不知道我姓什么
and you don't know my last name.
只要你能说出来我的姓
I will name every drink in this bar after you
我就用你名字命名这里的每一种酒
if you can tell me my last name.
那也太容易搞混了
Well, that just seems confusing.
你怎么知道客人点的是哪一种酒呢
How will you know what people are ordering?
我到底姓什么  马修
What's my last name, Marshall?
你叫卡尔
It's Carl...
二世
...'s Junior.
祝我好运吧  各位
Okay, wish me luck, everyone.
马到成功
Break a leg...
怎么回事
What the hell?
不要和她说话
Do not talk to her.
怎么回事  你们是谁
What-what... Who are you?
我们是二十个月之后的衣帽间女孩
We are 20-Months-From-Now- Coat-Check-Girl.
可你们是两个人
But there's two of you.
没错  因为如果你走过和她聊天
Right, because if you go over there and you talk to her,
二十个月之后  就会出现我们两人中的一种结局
20 months from now, it's gonna end in one of two ways.
要不就是你厌烦了我
Either you are gonna get sick of me.
我给你做了马芬松饼
I made you muffins
因为你的中间名叫马芬
because of your nickname: Muffin.
或是
Or...
我开始厌倦你  和你的蠢习惯
I am gonna get sick of you and your stupid habits.
别再录新闻了  你永远追不上的
Stop DVR-ing the news. You're never gonna catch up.
别说了
Oh, stop it,
你把他吓坏了
you're scaring him off.
对了  我怀孕了
By the way, I'm pregnant.
她没有
No, she's not.
好吧  我没有
Okay, no, I'm not,
但至少让你开心了一秒钟  对吗
but that made you happy for a second, right?
-请闭嘴  -好了  等等
- Please shut up. - Okay, wait,
你是说命中注定没结果吗
so you're saying it's doomed completely?
我们之中肯定有人会厌倦对方
One of us is just guaranteed to get sick of the other
然后提出分手吗
and call it quits?
你约会过这么多女人  泰德
You've been dating for a long time, Ted.
有碰到过其它结果吗
Has it ever gone any other way?
看这个
Look at this one.
谢谢
Thank you so much.
你看起来有些郁闷啊
Hey. Hey, you look kind of down.
喝杯罗宾・特布罗斯基  我请
Have a Robin Scherbatsky, on me.
如果莉莉让我跳舞  根本不会有这种事
None of this would have happened if Lily had let me dance.
宝贝  等等
Baby, wait.
老天  你还在念叨这个吗
God, you're still clinging to that?
马修  没关系
Marshall, it doesn't matter,
就算斗舞你也会输  知道为什么吗
'cause you'd lose anyway, and you know why?
因为我是亮晶晶  贱人
'Cause I'm Sparkles, bitch.
你觉得你可以赢我吗
Oh, and you think you can step to me?
你觉得你可以舞出你人生
You think you can step up to the streets?
电影原名是Step Up 2: The Streets
赢过我吗
To me?
你觉得你可以赢过我  舞出你人生吗
You think you can step up over me to the streets?
我想我们永远不会知道  因为你不允许...
I guess we'll never know because you are not allowed...
等等
Wait, wait.
这是我的曲子
That's my jam.
谁在放我的曲子
Who's playing my jam?
-一舞决胜负  -谁怕你
- Dance-off.  - You're on.
我还是回家吧
I think I'm gonna head home.
我理解
I understand.
你不想阻止我吗
What, you're not gonna try and stop me?
我如何阻止你
And how would I try and stop you?
不知道  告诉我人生苦短
I don't know, by telling me life is short,
如果有机会碰到美丽
and if you ever come across a beautiful,
激动疯狂的时刻
exciting, crazy moment in it,
就得在那一刻消失之前
you got to seize it while you can
紧紧把握住
before that moment's gone?
泰德  这一刻早已结束了
Ted, this moment already is gone.
"明尼苏达海啸"
The whole Minnesota Tidal Wave thing
是五年前的事了
happened five years ago.
这些只是你的回忆
It's just a memory.
而其余的事情
And the rest of this
从未发生
never happened.
现在  马修和莉莉在楼上
Right now, Marshall and Lily are upstairs,
哄马文睡觉
trying to get Marvin to go back to sleep.
罗宾和我在选婚宴承办商
Robin and I are trying to decide on a caterer.
你整晚坐在这里
And you've been sitting here all night,
盯着一张机器人对战摔跤手的票
staring at a single ticket to Robots vs. Wrestlers
因为我们四个人没时间出来
because the rest of us couldn't come out.
看看周围  泰德
Look around, Ted.
你是孤身一人
You're all alone.
孩子们  2013年4月那个寒冷的夜晚
Kids, it's been almost 20 years
已经过去二十年了
since that cold April night in 2013,
我可以肯定地告诉你们
and I can safely tell you,
如果我能回到过去  重新过那一晚
if I could go back in time and relive that night,
我绝对不会去看机器人对战摔跤手
there's no way in hell I'd go to Robots vs. Wrestlers.
不  我会回家
No, I'd go home.
我会去我的旧公寓
I'd go to my old apartment,
看看我的旧家具  所有的旧家当
see all my old furniture, my old stuff.
我会看看我的旧制图桌
I'd see my old drafting table,
我设计的第一栋大楼就是在上面画的
where I sketched out my first building.
我会坐在旧沙发上
I'd sit on that old couch
闻着三层楼下传来的印度菜香味
and smell the Indian food cooking three stories below.
我会去莉莉和马修的家
I'd go to Lily and Marshall's place,
回到那个有着无限美好记忆的客厅
be back in that old living room where so many things happened.
我会看看宝宝
I'd see the baby.
我不知道你们是否可以想象
I don't know if you can picture me holding
我把你们身高两米的马文大哥举过头顶
your six-foot-seven cousin Marvin over my head,
但当时我可以
but back then I could.
我会去找巴尼和罗宾喝一杯
I'd go have a drink with Barney and Robin,
看着他们为婚宴承办商吵架
watch them fight about their caterer
或是不管他们那晚吵什么
or whatever it was they were fighting about that night.
但这些都不是我想做的第一件事
But none of those things is the thing I'd do first.
你们知道我做的第一件事会是什么吗
You know the thing I'd do first?
你好
Hi.
我是泰德・莫斯比
I'm Ted Mosby.
从现在开始的45天之后
And exactly 45 days from now,
我们会相遇
you and I are gonna meet,
我们会坠入爱河
and we're gonna fall in love,
我们会结婚
and we're gonna get married,
我们会有两个孩子
and... we're gonna have two kids.
我们会深爱他们  也会深爱彼此
And we're gonna love them and each other so much.
虽然这些还有45天之遥
All that is 45 days away.
但现在我在这里
But I'm here now,
我想是因为
I guess, because...
我想和你多在一起45天
I want those extra 45 days with you.
我想珍惜这每一天
I want each one of them.
即使没有这45天
Look, and if I can't have them,
我也要拥有被你男朋友冲我脸上来一拳
I'll take the 45 seconds before your boyfriend shows up
之前的45秒
and punches me in the face,
因为
because...
我爱你
I love you.
我会永远爱你
I'm always gonna love you,
一生一世  生死不渝
till the end of my days and beyond.
你给我等着
You'll see.
有什么事吗
Can I help you?
你是路易斯吧
Oh, hey, it's, uh, Louis, right?
没事
It's okay.
没什么
It's fine, um...
我爱上了你的女朋友
I'm in love with your girlfriend,
我们会结婚
and, uh, we're gonna get married.
什么
What?
各位  这一刻我等了二十年
Okay, guys, I've been waiting 20 years for this.
跟我们练习时一样
Just like we practiced.
不准出错  准备好了吗
No mistakes, ready?
一  二  一二三四
One, two, a-one, two, three, four.
很久 *
* For the longest
Billy Joel - The Longest Time
很久以来 *
* For the longest time
很久 *
* For the longest
很久以来 *
* For the longest time
如果你今晚跟我分别 *
* If you said good-bye to me tonight
我依然有 *
* There would still
华丽乐章可写 *
* be music left to write
我别无选择 *
* What else could I do?
是你赋予我灵感 *
* I'm so inspired by you
这是我很久以来  未曾有过的感觉 *
* That hasn't happened for the longest time.